[

  {
    "question": "What is Flutter?",
    "options": ["A web browser", "A mobile development framework", "A programming language", "A database"],
    "answer": "A mobile development framework"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who developed Flutter?",
    "options": ["Apple", "Google", "Facebook", "Microsoft"],
    "answer": "Google"
  },
  {
    "question": "What language is used to write Flutter apps?",
    "options": ["Java", "Kotlin", "Dart", "Swift"],
    "answer": "Dart"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget is used for layouts in Flutter?",
    "options": ["Container", "Column", "Row", "All of the above"],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which command is used to create a new Flutter project?",
    "options": ["flutter init", "flutter create", "flutter start", "flutter new"],
    "answer": "flutter create"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence of asynchronous Flutter events is known as a:",
    "options": ["Flow", "Stream", "Series", "Current"],
    "answer": "Stream"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you add a dependency in a Flutter project?",
    "options": ["Edit the main.dart file", "Edit the pubspec.yaml file", "Edit the index.html file", "Edit the AndroidManifest.xml file"],
    "answer": "Edit the pubspec.yaml file"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a method to pass data to a StatefulWidget?",
    "options": ["setState()", "final variable", "constructor", "InheritedWidget"],
    "answer": "constructor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget is used to display a list of items in Flutter?",
    "options": ["Column", "Row", "Stack", "ListView"],
    "answer": "ListView"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which widget in Flutter is used to capture user input?",
    "options": ["Text", "Icon", "TextField", "Scaffold"],
    "answer": "TextField"
  }
]
